太好了  你在家
Oh, good, you're home.
听着  你得帮我埋个尸体
Listen, you got to help me bury a body.
(忆往昔)
他的真名是鲁弗斯·特纳
His real name's Rufus Turner.
猎魔人
He's a hunter.
是你的老友吗
One of your old friends?
-你见过这个男人吗  -没
- Have you seen this man? - No.
我没要你帮我
I ain't asking for no help.
没见过这个傻叉
Never seen that dick.
我没征求你的允许
I'm not asking for your permission.
-你怎么知道他是个傻叉  -我猜的
- How you know he's a dick? - Lucky guess.
想我了吗
Miss me?
每次我们一起埋尸体
He always used to pull
他总是用老套的
the old "can't work on the sabbath" card
"不能在安息日工作"搪塞我
whenever we had to bury a body.
教了我一些关于
Taught me a thing or two about...
世间邪恶生物的事
what's really out there.
很快  我们就一起上路
Pretty soon, we were riding together.
一起合作了多年
worked like that for years,
有点像你们俩小子
kind of like you two knuckleheads.
就像以前一样
Just like old times.
我开车就行
Long as I get to drive.
当然不行
Hell no.
(如今)
(密执根州  大急流城)
我没生气  亲爱的  我就是忙不过来
I'm not mad, honey. I'm just outnumbered.
这地方的状况比我们预期的差多了
This place is way more of a fixer-upper than we thought.
我开始明白
Like, I'm starting to see
这房子为什么那么久没卖出去了
why it was on the market for so long.
不  我知道  你说得对
No, I know. You're right.
你说得对  一个个房间的来
You're right. One room at a time...
先从这难看的墙纸开始
Starting with this awful wallpaper.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯  我也爱你  玛雅
Yeah, love you, too. Love you, too, Maya.
再见
Okay, bye.
凯特
Kat?!
-凯特  -妈妈
- Kat?! - Mommy?
房子里有不好的东西
Something... something bad is in the house.
你就是做恶梦了  亲爱的
It was just a nightmare, honey.
但我听到了脚步声
But I heard footsteps.
我们为什么非要搬来这里
Why did we have to move here?
我房间为什么这么冷
And why is it so cold in my room?
是啊  这里真是挺冷的
Yeah, it is cold in here, huh?
但炉子明天就能修好  所以
But the furnace is going to be fixed tomorrow, so...
你得耐心点  好吗
Just got to be patient, okay?
我们都是
We all do.
-还需要点什么吗  -我渴了
- Can I get you anything? - I'm thirsty.
好  马上给你拿杯水上来
Okay, one glass of water coming right up,
然后就继续睡觉
But then back to sleep.
好吗
Okay?
好
Okay.
妈妈
Mama?
[邪恶力量 第11季第16集]
好了
All right.
阿玛拉全无消息
Nothing on Amara.
小卡也是
Nothing on Cass.
别泄气  我们会赢的  记得吗
Keep your head up. We're gonna win this, remember?
是啊  但那是两周毫无进展之前的自信
Yeah, that was before two weeks of squat.
没人说会轻松的
Yeah, well, look, nobody said it was gonna be easy.
你懂的  我们现在先猎魔
You know the drill... meantime, we hunt.
看看
Check this out.
绯村直树说她的女儿被什么灵体袭击了
Naoki Himura said her little girl was attacked by an entity.
-孩子陷入昏迷了  -是啊
- Kid's in a coma? - Yeah.
唯一的伤痕  被妈妈称为
Only sign of trauma is what the mom is describing as a
是据信袭击者留下的手印
handprint from the alleged attacker,
但当时屋内没有别人  所以
but no one else was in the house at the time, so...
复仇鬼魂  恶作剧鬼
So a vengeful spirit, poltergeist?
值得一探究竟  就几小时的路程
It's worth finding out. It's only a couple hours away.
你真觉得我们现在应该放弃主要目标吗
You really think now is the time to take our eye off the prize?
迪恩  我们不能干等线索出现
Dean, we can't just sit around and... and wait for a lead.
再说  能办成点事也不错
Plus, it'd be nice to get a win.
这案子似乎没什么难度
This case seems like a layup.
得了  我们什么时候办过没难度的案子
Yeah, when was the last time we had a layup?
我妻子在努力赶回来
My wife is flying back,
但她的航班在伦敦延误了  所以
but her flight's been delayed in London, so...
我只能一个人面对
I'm alone in all this.
我们会尽力帮助你
Well, we're to help however we can.
多谢  但是
I appreciate that, but...
联调局为什么要对这种事感兴趣
Why would the FBI have any interest in this?
我们只是在尽职
Just...doing our due diligence.
你能不能跟我们
You know what? Why don't you go ahead
说说袭击当晚的事
and tell us about the night of the attack?
没人相信发生了袭击
Nobody believes there was an attack.
就连网民都认为我是疯了
E-even the internet thinks I'm crazy.
我们不那么认为
Well, we don't.
凯特惊叫着醒来
Okay, well, Kat woke up screaming.
我以为她只是做恶梦了
I thought she was just having a nightmare.
但她说她听到了脚步声
But she said she heard footsteps
还感觉屋子里有不好的东西
and that she felt something...bad in the house.
你也听到脚步声了吗
Did you also hear footsteps?
没有
No.
你还注意到其他的了吗
Did you notice anything else...
冷点或灯光闪烁
cold spots or flickering lights?
还真有
Yeah, actually.
她房间的灯熄灭了
The lights were out in her room,
而且很冷
a-and it was cold in there.
这意味着什么
W-what does that mean?
我们可以去你家看看吗
Would you mind if we went and had a look at your house?
当然  如果你们认为这会有帮助的话
Sure, yeah, I mean, if you think it's gonna help.
我藏了把钥匙
There's a-a hide-a-key
在前门一块彩石下面
under a painted rock by the front door.
好  多谢帮忙
Great. Thank you for your help.
不客气
Yeah, sure.
打扰
Excuse me.
有什么能帮你们的吗
Can I help you boys?
或许
Maybe.
赖泽特别探员
Special Agent Rizer.
这位是我搭档  比恩特别探员
This is my partner, Special Agent Bean.
-我们  -为什么联调局
- We, uh... - Why do the FBI
老跑来看那栋房子
keep coming back to that house?
什么
Excuse me?
个把年前  联调局就来过
A handful of years ago, the FBI came here.
我是邻里联防队的队长
I'm the head of the neighborhood watch, you know?
所以我问过那两位探员是来做什么的
So I asked the two agents what they were doing here.
他们怎么说的
And what'd they say?
什么都没说
Not a thing.
他们是我见过的最粗鲁的两个人了
They were two of the rudest people I'd ever met.
这两位探员会不会是
By any chance, were these agents, um...
比较年长的人
elder statesmen?
对
Yeah.
你们的朋友吗
Friends of yours?
(个把年前)
你为什么睡在车里  鲍比
Why are you sleeping in your car, Bobby?
现在是午休时间
It's lunchtime.
叫我来干什么
What the hell am I doing here?
你要帮我办案
You're helping me with a case...
我在电话里不是说了
Like I told you on the phone.
你没事吧
You okay?
天启即将到来
The apocalypse is on the horizon,
你还要来捉鬼
and you want to hunt a damn ghost?
除非你小憩的时候想到如何
Well, unless you found a way to stop the end of the world
阻止世界末日了  我们在那事上毫无进展
during your little siesta, we got Jack all on any of that business.
我知道你就在这附近
You know, I knew you were in the area.
听说这里可能有案子
Heard about this possible little gig...
我觉得能办成点事也不错
I thought a win would be nice.
等等
Oh, wait.
我是你的后援吗
I'm supposed to be your friggin' backup?
是啊
Yeah.
如果你对"后援"的理解
Well, if by "backup" you mean
是我看着你把脏活儿累活都干了的话
you do all the heavy lifting while I watch.
今天是安息日
I-it's shabbat.
-你开玩笑吗  -绝对不是
- Are you serious? - Deadly.
你还开车过来了呢  这就不违反教规了
You drove over here! Ain't that against the rules?
少说话
Less talking.
多猎魔
More hunting.
打扰
Excuse me.
你们来这儿做什么
What are you gentlemen... here for?
联调局  女士
FBI, ma'am.
特别探员里格斯
Special Agent Riggs.
我搭档  特别探员莫陶
My partner, Special Agent Murtaugh.
我们来办联调局公务
We're on official FBI business.
不用担心
Nothing to worry about.
我是这里的邻里联防队队长  先生
Well, I am in charge of the neighborhood watch here, sir.
我要知道你们究竟是来办什么公务的
I would like to know what this official business is you're here about.
是与你无关的公务  女士
It's officially none of your damn business, ma'am.
你有好声好气过吗
Were you ever nice?
1985年  这辈子最糟的一年
1985... worst year of my life.
这里到处有反应
I'm getting hits everywhere down here.
楼上也是
Yeah, upstairs, as well.
好吧  那么怎么回事
All right, so, what?
鲍比和鲁弗斯当年在这儿办过案
Bobby and Rufus worked a case here back in the day?
我们以前遇到过多鬼宅
I mean, we've had houses with multiple ghosts before.
不对劲  迪恩
I don't know, Dean.
这世界是小  但也没那么小
I mean, the world is small, but it's not that small.
我车后箱里有几本鲍比的日记
I've got a couple of Bobby's old journals in the trunk.
我们去翻翻
Why don't we dig into those,
再查查房子的历史  看看怎么回事
dig into the history of the house, see what's what?
当时是我们搬进来的第一晚
It was our first night in the house.
我们都上床了  然后
We had all gone to bed, and then
我儿子  威尔  他呼救
Will, My son, he called out for help.
说他听到了奇怪的声音  像是脚步声
Said he heard a strange noise, sounded like footsteps.
我丈夫和我跑进了他的房间
My husband and I ran to his room,
但等我们到时
but, uh, by the time we got there,
我的孩子已经失去意识躺在地上了
my baby was on the ground unconscious.
你那晚还注意到别的什么了吗
Did you notice anything else that night...
冷点  灯光闪烁
cold spots or lights flickering?
还真有
Actually, yes.
都有
Both.
威尔的房间很冷  灯也熄灭了
Will's room was cold, and the lights were out.
医生不知道他是出了什么问题
The doctors don't know what's wrong with him.
除了他脚踝上的奇怪痕迹
Apart from the strange mark on his ankle
没有其他外伤
there's no sign of trauma.
什么叫"奇怪痕迹"
How do you mean "strange mark"?
看上去像手印
It looks like a handprint.
多谢
Well, thank you very much.
你知道附近有什么比较经济的汽车旅馆吗
Uh, do you know of any affordable motels in the area?
(汽车旅馆)
听着
Get this...
经理说几年前有两位联调局探员在这儿住过
the manager said two FBI agents stayed here years ago,
图个吉利  我要了一样的房间
so I got the same room for luck.
抱歉打扰您读书了  教皇陛下
Sorry to disturb reading time, your holiness.
别跟我搞宗教迫害  鲍比
Do not religiously persecute me, Bobby.
告诉我
Tell me something, man...
你之前为什么睡在车里
why were you sleeping in your car earlier?
警方没有什么进展
Cops got nothing.
你真要不回答我啊
Oh, you're really ‭not gonna answer me, huh?
但我拿到了地产经纪人的房屋报告
But I got the realtor's report on the house.
你买下房子前  他们有法律义务告诉你
'cause they legally have to tell you who died in a house
谁死在那里过
before you buy it.
看你多聪明
Look at you being all smart.
谁死了
So, who died?
房子里死过两个人
There were two deaths at the house.
第一个是死于意外  别笑
The first was accidental... and don't laugh...
一个人被鸡骨头噎死了
a dude choked on a chicken bone.
另一个是凶杀
And the other was a murder.
一名男子开枪打死妻子
A man shot his wife.
鲍比和鲁弗斯
Well, Bobby and Rufus were...
绝对在这儿找过鬼
definitely on a ghost hunt.
"密执根州  大急流城
Uh, "Grand Rapids, Michigan.
跟混蛋寻找可能鬼魂"
Possible ghost hunt with Jackass."
就这些了
That's all he wrote?
嗯  看来鲍比没能完成日记
Yeah, I guess Bobby never got around to finishing it...
懒散
Slacker.
那么他们要么是在找鸡骨头哥
Okay, so, they were ‭either hunting chicken bone
要么是那个混蛋
or asshat.
一个鬼当时就被制服了
One ghost breaks bad back then.
另一个一直蛰伏到现在
The other's been marinating until now.
我认为唯一的问题是
The only problem I see is
我们不知道鲍比和鲁弗斯究竟烧了哪具尸骨
that we don't know what bones Bobby and Rufus burned,
所以我们可能得挖两个坟
so we might have to... dig up two graves.
未必吧  迪恩
I don't know, Dean.
我觉得没那么简单
I think there's more to it than that.
这里面感觉不对劲
I mean... I mean, something's not right.
太轻松了
It's all a little too easy.
简单轻松我也不介意
Hey, easy like Sunday morning works for me, okay?
我们赶紧了事  继续去追踪阿玛拉
We can wrap this up quick, get back to hunting Amara.
把小卡弄回来
Get Cass back.
你自己也说
I mean, hey, you said it yourself...
这案子按说该没难度的
This case is supposed to be a layup, right?
是啊  但我虽然不愿承认  你是对的
Yeah, but, as much as I hate to admit it, you were right.
我们什么时候办过没难度的
You know, I mean, when have we ever had one of those?
得了
Come on.
你觉得鲍比和鲁弗斯当初
You think Bobby ‭and Rufus wasted any time
浪费时间为这种事争执了吗
arguing ‭about this kind of crap?
走吧
Let's go.
该死  鲁弗斯  你为什么要把
Damn it, Rufus, why do you have to make
什么事都想的那么复杂
everything so friggin' complicated?
怎么复杂了
What's complicated?
我就是说  不是鬼魂
I'm just saying it's not a ghost.
是貘
It's a baku.
什么
What?
一种日本
A Japanese...
我知道貘是什么  你个蠢蛋
I know what a baku is, you dumbass.
我们在阿拉斯加一起猎过一只
We hunted one together in Alaska.
好吧  我跟你赌一瓶尊尼威士忌
All right, I'll bet you a bottle of Johnnie
这个是貘
that it's a baku.
那准备去给我买尊尼威士忌吧
Well, get ready ‭to buy me a bottle of Johnnie
因为这才不是貘
'cause it ain't a baku.
就是个鬼  简单明了
It's a ghost, plain and simple,
我们越早把骨头烧了
And the sooner ‭we get to burnin' bones,
也就越早能继续去琢磨
the sooner we can get back to figuring out
怎么拯救世界
how to save the world.
走吧  我们还得挖坟呢
Now, come on. We got diggin' to do.
我们  我们
"We"? "We"?!
我要说多少次
How many times ‭do I got to tell you, man?
你洗洗这破车不行吗
Would it kill you to ‭at least wash this damn thing?
这里面闻着像路毙动物炖菜
It smells like ‭roadkill Casserole in here.
闭嘴  你个白痴
Just shut up, you idjit.
该死
Son of a bitch!
灰
Ashes.
挖坟肯定有更轻松的方式吧
There's got to be an easier way to dig graves.
你为什么停下了
Why are you stopping?
因为该你了
'cause it's your turn.
什么该我了
What... what my turn?
鲍比  看我的唇形  鲍比
Hey, yo, yo, Bobby, ‭Bobby, read my lips, Bobby.
我不能帮你  好吗
I cannot help you, all right?
今天是安息日
It is sabbath.
太阳已经下山了  给我挖
It is after sundown, so get to diggin'.
说得好
Good catch.
鲍比  我能问个问题吗
Bobby, ‭can I ask you something?
只要不是关于
As long as it's not about...
我之前为什么睡在车里就行
why I was sleeping in my car earlier.
你之前为什么睡在车里
Why were you sleeping in your car earlier?
这几周以来
Been burnin' the midnight oil...
经常开夜车
Last couple of weeks.
一连几天不睡觉
Up for days...
想找办法阻止天启
looking for ways to stop the apocalypse.
寻找任何线索
Looking for...anything.
萨姆和迪恩就处在这事中央
Sam and Dean are right in the middle of this thing.
我担心我的孩子们  鲁弗斯
I'm worried about my boys, Rufus.
你的孩子们
Your boys?
好吧  好吧
All right. Okay.
熊爸爸
Papa bear.
但你最清楚的  鲍比
But you know ‭more than anyone, Bobby...
就算我们找到办法维持世界运转
Even if we find a way ‭to keep the world spinning...
也不是每个人都能安全脱身
Not everyone's gonna be on that bus ride home.
牺牲  大局
Sacrifice, greater good...
什么的
all that jazz.
我知道
Yeah. I know.
猎魔最老的规矩  鲍比
Oldest rule of hunting, Bobby...
你不能拯救每个人
You can't save everyone.
不是吧
Oh, come on!
Oh, come on.
鲍比一向是个做事彻底的人
Yeah, Bobby always was thorough.
两罐灰  那么我们要找的不是鬼
Two ash cans, which means we're not hunting a ghost.
我早说了
I told you.
嗯嗯  你就对了这么一次
Yeah, yeah, you... you were right for once.
那么我们要找的是什么
So, then, what the hell are we hunting?
嗯
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢  多谢了  好
Thank you. I appreciate it. All right.
-这事以前发生过  -这事以前发生过
- This has happened before. - This has happened before.
你先说
You first.
过来
Just...come here.
理查德兹医生
Dr. Richards?
这位是我的搭档  赖泽特别探员
This is my partner, Special Agent Rizer.
这位是理查德兹医生  她已经退休了
This is Dr. Richards. Now, she's retired, but...
我在医院里还有朋友
I still have friends on staff here,
所以当我听说一家有两人
so when I heard that two family members
陷入无法解释的昏迷
had lapsed into unexplained comas,
我就来看看能不能帮忙
I came in to see if I could help.
之前发生这种事时你也在吗
So, you were here when this happened before?
是的
Yes.
当时也有两位联调局探员就案件找过我
Two FBI agents spoke to me about that case, too.
玛丽·亨德森回家去拿儿子最喜欢的娃娃
Mary Henderson went home to get her son's favorite doll.
但之后便不再接听电话
When she didn't answer any calls,
于是她丈夫报了警
her husband phoned the police.
他们发现了她
They found her.
她...
And she's...
跟儿子一样
Same as her son.
脚踝上有奇怪痕迹  再没别的了
Weird mark on the ankle. That's it.
是昏迷了吗
So, it's some kind of coma?
我是没见过这样的
None like I've ever seen.
什么意思
How do you mean?
他们的生命体征衰竭得很快
Well, their vitals are fading rapidly.
如果他们不尽快转好
If they don't show ‭some signs of rallying soon,
我担心他们会撑不过去
I'm worried we may lose them.
究竟怎么回事
So, what happened?
怎么回事  我也不知道
What happened? I have no idea.
第二天  母亲和儿子都清醒了
The next day, mother and son woke up,
两人都没事了
both perfectly fine.
当然了  我希望这次也能如此
Obviously, I hope the same thing happens here,
但他俩
but these two...
他们的生命体征也在衰竭
Their vitals are failing, as well, so...
好吧  多谢配合
Okay. Thank you for your time.
鲍比和鲁弗斯猎的东西
So, Bobby and Rufus' case?
是啊  又回来了
Yeah, it's back.
不管是个什么东西
Whatever it was... is.
你有什么发现
What did you find?
我跟当年发现了
I talked to the local P.D....
玛丽·亨德森并送她来这家医院的
The actual cops that found Mary Henderson back in the day
当地警察通了话
and brought her to this hospital.
亨德森夫妇还在吗
Are the Hendersons still around?
玛丽·亨德森
Mary Henderson?
-我们是特别探员  -天呐
- We're Special Agents... - Oh, God.
又发生了吗  我...
Is it happening again? Am I...
我儿子有危险吗
Is my son in danger?
不不  一切都好
No, no. E-everything's... everything's fine.
但我们...想跟你谈谈
But we... we would like to talk to you
你儿子经历的那件事
about what happened with your son.
紧接着  我就在医院醒来
Next thing you know, I woke up in the hospital,
一位联调局探员告诉我
and one ‭of the FBI agents told me
永远别碰起居室里的墙纸
to never touch the wallpaper in the sitting room.
有两个人身陷危险
Two people are in great danger.
你能记起任何事  任何细节吗
A-anything you can remember, any little detail...
我
I, um...
我陷入昏迷时  做了个梦
When I was in the coma, I had a dream.
更像是噩梦
I mean, it was more like a nightmare.
就像
It was...
我还在房子里  但又不是
like I was in the house, but it wasn't the house.
一切都很黑
Everything was dark.
看上去很模糊
And it looked faded.
起初  我是一个人
And at first, I was alone,
然后我开始看到一些东西
but then I-I started to see things.
你究竟看到了什么
What did you see exactly?
我丈夫
My husband.
他死了
He was dead.
我闭上眼睛  再睁开的时候
I closed my eyes, ‭and when I opened them...
他就不见了
he was gone.
我想离开  但做不到
I tried to leave the house, but I couldn't,
然后我就开始看到他们
and then that's ‭when I started to see them.
幽灵还是什么的  我也不知道
Spirits or something. I don't know.
我说了  现在都很模糊了
Like I said, it's all...faded now.
就是个噩梦
It was just... a bad dream.
你醒来后发生了什么
And what happened when you woke up?
我们尽力向前看
Well, we tried to move on, you know?
但我甩不掉那种不舒服的感觉
But I couldn't shake the bad feeling.
所以我们把房子卖掉了
So we put the house up for sale.
然后房市崩盘
Then, the market crashed.
最终  我们不再还按揭了
So, finally, we just walked on the mortgage...
所以现在我们只能租房  恐怕要永远如此了
which is why we now rent and probably will forever.
但毁掉信用也值得
Destroying our credit was worth it, though.
只要能远离那栋破房子就行
Anything to get away from that damn house.
迪恩
Dean.
看看
Check this out.
看这个
Look at this.
认得吗
You recognize that?
有点印象
Vaguely.
看来他们重装修的时候破坏了封印
Looks like they broke a seal when they were redecorating.
我们究竟在猎什么
What the hell are we hunting?
(坠落天使)
我好像查到了
I got it... I think.
噬魂怪
A soul eater?
那是什么
The hell is that?
吃灵魂的不死怪物  所以叫这个
Undead creature that feeds on souls, hence the name.
存活于我们的世界和异世界之间
They exist in a place between our world and another.
噬魂怪住进一栋房子  随后
a soul eater moves ‭into a house, and once it does,
根据传说  便会筑巢
it makes what the lore refers to as a nest.
"存在于时间和空间之外的地方"
"A place that exists outside of time and space"
巢穴看上去  感觉上去
The nest looks and feels like
跟噬魂怪所居住的房子很像
whatever house the soul eater is in.
那么玛丽陷入昏迷的时候那不是做恶梦
So, Mary didn't have a nightmare when she was in her coma.
记得吗  她说她当时在她家里
Remember, she said that she was in her house
但又不是她的家  那是巢穴
but it wasn't her house... she was in the nest.
噬魂怪并不存在于这里或那边
The soul eaters aren't really here or there,
但他们可以积蓄足够力量
but apparently ‭they can muster enough strength
将被害人的灵魂
t-to yank their vics' souls
从这个世界  拽入他们的巢穴
out of this world and into their nest.
被害人被拽入巢穴后
And then, as soon ‭as the vic's in the nest,
他们就不在我们的时间空间里了
t-they're outside of our space and time.
好吧  那玛丽
Okay, well, ‭what about Mary, uh,
看到她死去的丈夫和儿子怎么解释
seeing her dead husband and her son?
据说  巢穴会扰乱被害人的神智
Apparently, the nest messes with their victim's head,
让他们看到所爱之人  让他们的灵魂受折磨
shows them things they love, parts of their soul in distress.
这样被害人的灵魂就容易受侵害
It keeps ‭the victim's soul vulnerable.
那现实世界的肉身会怎么样
So, what happens to the meat suits in the real world?
他们会在现实世界里憔悴死亡
They wither and die in the real world.
所以玛丽和她儿子的生命体征才会衰竭
Which explains Mary ‭and her son's failing vitals.
噬魂怪
And the soul eater...
会关闭巢穴  去下一家
closes up the nest ‭and moves on to the next house.
那还留在巢里的灵魂呢
What happens to the remains of the souls in the nest?
他们也会憔悴
Well, they wither, too,
但还留在噬魂怪身边
but they stay with the soul eater,
让它捕不到猎物时可以享用
keeping it fed in lean times,
就像反刍食物
sort of like a cud.
简直太恶心了
Well, that sounds perfectly awful.
我们得干掉这混蛋
We got to kill this bastard
否则亨德森家的俩人要死了
before the Hendersons' bodies wither and die.
据传说  他们是杀不死的
According to the lore, they can't be killed.
但我确定  可以困住他们
But I'm pretty sure they can be trapped.
我觉得我以前遇到过一次噬魂怪
I think I've faced ‭one of these soul eaters before.
真的吗
You serious?
是发生在田纳西州古德利茨维尔的一桩案子
It was a case down ‭in Goodlettsville, Tennessee.
鲍比接到另一名猎人的电话
Bobby got a call from another hunter,
名叫哈维
a guy named Harvey.
他当时在猎魔
Uh, he was hunting a case.
据传房子里满是恶作剧鬼
House was rumored to be chock-full of poltergeists.
但他找不到可以烧的骨头
But he couldn't find the bones to burn,
于是便叫鲍比去支援
so he calls Bobby for backup.
鲍比急忙赶过去
Bobby hightails it down there.
他拿着猎枪  冲进了房子
He goes into the house, buckshots, guns blazing.
不行
No, no, no, no, no!
别用你的话来说
Do not tell me how you tell it.
告诉我真实情况
Tell me how it really happened.
我一踏进那间房子
I stepped one foot inside that house
就吓尿了
and filled my drawers.
你都能感到那股邪恶感  鲁弗斯
You could feel the badness, Rufus.
哈维躺在地板上  陷入了昏迷
I found Harv on the floor, in a coma.
我想帮他
I tried to help,
但他似乎已经躺了好几天了
but it looked like he'd been there for days.
然后  我听到了脚步声
And then, I heard footsteps.
我被困住了
I was trapped.
但我有个古凯尔特符文
But I had this old celtic sigil.
算是
Sort of a...
"紧急情况下打碎玻璃"用的东西
"break glass in case ‭of emergency" sort of thing.
据说能困住怪物  但老实说
Supposed to trap monsters, but to be honest,
那东西以前从未好使过
the damn thing never worked before.
但我只有这一个办法  我就试了
But it was all I had, so I started.
要说这房子感觉不妙
And this house is bad juju?
这下感觉更糟了
It just got a hell of a lot worse.
等我完成了符文
Then, I finished the sigil, and once I did,
房子又回归正常了
the house went back to normal.
那
And, um...
哈维呢
Harv?
他没醒过来
He never did wake up.
嗯
Yeah, well...
最老的规矩  鲍比
Oldest rule, Bobby.
最老的规矩
Oldest rule.
你真困住了一个噬魂怪
So, uh, you actually trapped a soul eater?
鲍比和鲁弗斯画了个符文
Bobby and Rufus put up their sigil
把噬魂怪困在巢里了
and trapped the soul eater in its nest.
嗯
Right.
然后它一直待在那里  直到直树不小心
Yeah, and it stayed there until Naoki accidentally
在装修的时候破坏了封印的符文
broke the sigil's seal when she redecorated.
嗯  噬魂怪就被释放了
Right, which set the soul eater free.
好吧  但如果符文只是困住了它
Okay, but if their sigil only trapped it,
那玛丽和儿子的灵魂是怎么离开巢穴的
then how did Mary and her son's souls get out of the nest?
或许  封印把灵魂逼出来了
Maybe the trap forced their souls out?
我不知道
I don't know.
这事肯定没这么简单
You know, there's got to be more to this.
可惜鲍比和鲁弗斯不能看到这一切
You know, it's too bad Bobby and Rufus aren't around to see stuff.
他们本会成为很棒的记录者
They'd have been great Men of Letters.
是啊  脾气大的老记录者  但是没错
Yeah, grumpy, old Men of Letters, but, yeah.
等等
Wait a second.
看看
Check this out.
看来记录者有办法
Looks like ‭the Men of Letters found a way
杀死噬魂怪
to kill soul eaters.
好厉害  怎么做
Awesome. How?
看来是用另一个符文
Well, looks like it's another sigil...
更复杂一些  血做的
more complicated, uh, made from blood.
割伤手  把符文
You cut your hand, and you paint this bad boy
画在房子里  同时再画一个
inside the house while the same thing is painted...
在巢穴里
inside the nest.
那么我们中一个得进去
Which means one of us has to go in there?
-嗯  -不行
- Yeah. - Not it.
哥们
Uh, dude...
我们再也不要
We are never settling anything
用那个蠢办法做决定了  再也不了
with that stupid game again... ever.
好吧  我画在这里  那么
All right. I'll paint here, so...
你
you...
把你的画在这里
paint yours here.
你的符文是准备程序
Now, your sigil sets the table.
我的是必杀技
Mine actually kills it.
好  血拿了
All right. You got your blood?
这里
Right here.
-好了  我们来吧  -好
- All right, let's do this. - Yeah.
如果没记错  接下来要难受了
If memory serves, things are about to get hairy.
要牵着手吗
You want to hold my hand?
继续画  毕加索
Keep painting, Picasso.
来抓我啊  你个混蛋
Come get me, you son of a bitch.
离我远点  你个混蛋
Stay away from me, you son of a bitch.
萨姆
Sam?
好吧
Okay.
鲁弗斯
Rufus?
天呐
Oh, God.
你是真的吗
Are you real?
威尔·亨德森
Will Henderson?
是的
Yes, sir.
我有麻烦了吗
Am I in trouble?
不不  孩子  不是的
No, no, no, son, not at all.
我叫鲍比·辛格
My name is Bobby Singer.
我是来
And I'm... I'm here to...
我也困在这里了
Well, I'm... I'm stuck here, too.
但是我会照顾你的  好吗
But, uh, I'm gonna take care of you, okay?
你看见你母亲了吗
Have you seen your mother?
没有
No.
你看到什么...奇怪的人了吗
H-have you seen anyone...strange?
你是指那些难过的人吗
You mean the sad people?
谁
The who?
他们就在你身后
They're right behind you.
他们看上去像是病了  你没看到吗
They look sick. You don't see them?
没
No.
但我们会离开这儿的
But, uh, we're gonna get out of here.
我的朋友会帮我们的
My friend is gonna help us.
鲍比
Bobby?
鲍比  鲍比
Bobby? Bobby?
鲍比
Bobby?
最老的规矩  鲍比  最老的规矩
Oldest damn rule, Bobby. Oldest rule.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好了  有我呢
All right, I got you.
撑住  好了
Stay with me. There we go.
我老得要做不动这种事了
I'm getting too old for this.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
是凯特吧
It's Kat, right?
认识你很高兴  凯特
It's nice to meet you, Kat.
我不该跟陌生人说话的
Not supposed to talk to strangers.
那是条好规矩
And that... that is a solid rule.
我叫迪恩·温彻斯特
My name is Dean Winchester.
瞧  我不是陌生人了吧
See? Now I'm not a stranger.
我是来带你离开的
I'm here to get you out of this place.
你见到你妈妈了吗
Have you seen your mom?
我看不到她
I can't see her.
这里现在太挤了
It's too crowded in here now.
我没看见别人啊
I-I don't see anybody.
你很快就会看到他们了
You'll see them soon.
我带你离开这儿怎么样
How about we get you out of here instead?
你妈妈就在这附近
Your mom is around here somewhere.
我们一起去找她  好吗
We'll look for her and stick together, okay?
妈妈
Mommy!
不  别  我说了我们得一起行动
No, wait. ‭I said "stick together""
搞什么
What the?
鲍比
Bobby?
打我  你朋友就死了
Shoot me, you kill your friend.
岩盐  鲍比受得了
Rock salt... Bobby can handle it.
好了
Now, now.
不必伤害任何人
No need to hurt anyone.
跟我走吧
Just come along with me...
进入巢穴
into the nest.
为什么
Why?
让你给我看一堆乱七八糟的东西
So you can show me a bunch of messed-up stuff in there
留着我帅气的身躯在外面发霉吗
while my fabulous body rots out here?
我不想去
I don't think I want to take that ride.
真漂亮
It's pretty.
谢谢
Thanks.
我不喜欢这里
I don't like it here.
我也是
Yeah, me, neither.
我弟弟
And my brother...
他在画一幅跟这个很像的画
he's making a painting just like this one.
等他完成了
And when he's done...
我们就能出去了  好吗
we're out of here, okay?
快点  萨姆  准备好了  我们开始吧
Come on, Sam, the table is set. Let's do this.
他们更多了
There's more of them now.
迪恩
Dean?
我不能允许你画完  孩子
I can't let you finish that finger painting, boy.
跟我进入巢穴吧
Just come with me into the nest.
我可以保护你不受黑暗伤害
I can keep you safe from the Darkness.
迪恩  听我说  我知道你还在里面
Dean, listen to me. I know you're in there.
抵抗它
Fight this!
鲁弗斯
Rufus...
我不能让你困住我
I can't let you trap me.
那我们就有麻烦了  是吧
Then, we got a problem then, don't we?
迪恩  停下来
Dean, stop this!
你哥哥想去找黑暗
Your brother wants to go to the Darkness.
他必须去  但我可以保护你
He needs to go, but I can keep you safe...
永远保护你们俩
Both of you... forever.
这可不妙
Yeah, that can't be good.
他们都走了
They're leaving.
鲍比  鲍比
Bobby? Bobby?!
你没事吧
You okay?
刚刚怎么回事
What the hell just happened?
迪恩  迪恩
Dean, Dean?
你没事吧  你没事吧
Are you good? Are you good?
好了  有我呢
All right, I got you.
怎么样
Well?
大家都醒了
Well, everybody's awake...
很开心
And happy.
究竟怎么回事
So, what happened?
那是个封印咒  我们也该被困住啊
It was a trap spell. We should be trapped, too.
是个貘  鲍比
It was a baku, Bobby.
我趁你睡觉时杀掉了它
I killed it while you slept.
你欠我一瓶尊尼威士忌哦
That'll be ‭one bottle of Johnnie, please.
才不是...
It wasn't a damn...
封印符文把你们的灵魂推了出来
The trap sigil pushed your souls out.
结案  不客气
Case closed. You're welcome.
我不喜欢这样
Uh, I don't like it.
谁管你喜不喜欢
Who gives a damn what you like?
接受胜利吧
Take the win.
好吧
Yeah, yeah.
你没事吧  鲍比
You okay, Bobby?
我没事
I'm fine.
你在巢穴里
You saw something...
看到了什么  是吧
in the nest, didn't you?
你看到什么了  鲍比
What'd you see, Bobby?
我那俩熊孩子
My boys.
他们两个
Both of them.
都死了
Both of them dead.
然后我看到了
And then, I saw...
我也不知道我看到的是什么
Well, I don't know what the hell I saw.
好吧
Yeah, well...
忘记最老的规矩吧  鲍比
Forget the oldest rule, Bobby.
你这是心软了吗  鲁弗斯
Are you gettin' soft on me, Rufus?
软个鬼
Yeah, soft this.
白痴
Idjit.
没事  我没事  我特别想回家
No, no, I'm okay. I can't wait to go home.
我还是不明白到底是怎么回事
Yeah, I still don't understand what the hell just happened.
你只需要知道  你的房子现在已经安全了
All you need to know is that your house is safe now.
不过你家厨房估计得重新装修一下
Your kitchen may need a remodel, though.
没事  我们想把房子卖了
Mm, that's okay. I think we're selling.
好吧
Fair enough.
好  你多保重
All right, take care of yourself.
谢谢你们...做的一切
Thank you... for everything.
(好吧  混蛋  你赢了  享用吧  鲁)
迪恩  你们没事吧
Dean. You boys okay?
我们没事  鲍比  你去哪了
Yeah, we're fine, Bobby. Where the hell have you been?
-我留了三通留言  -我...
- I've left three messages. - Well, I was...
缅因州有一条疑似莉莉丝的线索
Look, I got a possible lead on Lilith in Maine,
但是我们在里诺办案
but we're on a case in Reno.
我把地址短信给你了
I texted you the address.
如果你闲够了的话
So, if you're done sitting on your ass...
继续午餐回顾  下面是另一首经典金曲
And here's another classic as our flashback lunch continues.
白痴
Idjits.
好吧
Okay.
话说  鲍比的日记里没提到他进入了巢穴
You know, Bobby's journal never mentioned him going into the nest.
实际上  什么都没写
It didn't say anything actually.
你觉得那真的是他  还是
You think it was really him or...
我不知道
I don't know.
也许就像你之前说的那样
Maybe it's like... like you said before,
鲍比和鲁弗斯的封印符文
that Bobby and Rufus' trap sigil
当时将他们的灵魂逼出了巢穴
forced their souls out of the nest back then
噬魂怪只是让我看到了幻象
and that the soul eater was just making me see things.
不过
However...
如果鲍比那时真进了巢穴
If Bobby did go into the nest back then...
你也说过巢穴存在于
And you said that the nest exists
空间和时间之外  那
outside of space and time... then...
理论上讲  他和我有可能
Well, theoretically, couldn't he and I have been there
同时存在于那里啊
at the same time? Right?
我头疼
My head hurts.
-那就去喝酒  把这事永远忘记吧  -好
- Well, let's get drunk and not think about this ever again. - Yeah.
不过我们得先去趟田纳西州
First, we got to stop in Tennessee, though...
鲍比之前那桩噬魂怪案
Bobby's old soul eater case.
他不会希望留下悬案  对吧
He wouldn't want any unfinished business on the books, you know?
好吧
Fine.
但这回换你进巢穴
But this time, you're going in the nest.
你说噬魂怪让你看见了好多东西
Hey, you said the soul eater made you see "things," plural.
你还看见了什么
So, what else did you see?
我看见你的尸体躺在地上
I saw you dead on the floor.
怎么了
What?
我们的日子是过得多糟糕
How messed up are our lives that
以至于你看见我的尸体还有点令人欣慰
you seeing a vision of dead me is actually kind of comforting?
是啊
Yeah.
接下来是今天最后一首经典金曲
And here's the last classic of the day.
跟"奥曼兄弟乐队"一起上路吧
Let's take it on the road with the Allman brothers.